const quizData = {
  "title": "NBA History Quiz",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What player is the NBA logo based on?",
      "options": ["Michael Jordan", "Larry Bird", "Jerry West", "Magic Johnson"],
      "answer": "Jerry West",
      "type": "single-answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the record for most points scored in a single game?",
      "options": ["100", "81", "70", "93"],
      "answer": "100",
      "type": "single-answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What player has the most MVP's in league history?",
      "options": ["Bill Russell", "LeBron James", "Micheal Jordan", "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"],
      "answer": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "type": "single-answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the last player to be drafted from high school to the NBA?",
      "options": ["Kobe Bryant", "Jermaine O'Neal", "Tracy McGrady", "Amir Johnson"],
      "answer": "Amir Johnson",
      "type": "single-answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the name of Seattle's former NBA team?",
      "options": ["Suns", "Supersonics", "Strikers", "Sparks"],
      "answer": "Supersonics",
      "type": "single-answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who holds the record for most points scored all time?",
      "options": ["Kobe Bryant", "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar", "LeBron James", "Wilt Chamerlain"],
      "answer": "LeBron James",
      "type": "single-answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following teams have won three consecutive championships (3-peat)?.",
      "options": ["Chicago Bulls", "Golden State Warriors", "Minneapolis Lakers", "Los Angeles Lakers"],
      "answers": ["Chicago Bulls", "Minneapolis Lakers", "Los Angeles Lakers"],
      "type": "multiple-answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following team names used to represent a team?",
      "options": ["Baltimore Bullets", "St. Louis Bombers", "Virgina Stallions", "Washington Capitols"],
      "answers": ["Baltimore Bullets", "St. Louis Bombers", "Washington Capitols"],
      "type": "multiple-answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which NBA teams have never won an NBA championship?",
      "options": ["Los Angeles Clippers", "New York Knicks", "Indiana Pacers", "Milwaukee Bucks"],
      "answers": ["Los Angeles Clippers", "Indiana Pacers"],
      "type": "multiple-answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many championships does the player with the most ever won have?",
      "answers": ["11", "eleven"],
      "type": "free-form"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the only team in NBA history to lose a championship series up 3-1?",
      "answers": ["golden state warriors"],
      "type": "free-form"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which player has the most NBA seasons played for their career?",
      "answers": ["lebron james"],
      "type": "free-form"
    }
  ]
}